<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AlertReceive</string>
    <string name="title_activity_actions_plans">ActionsPlans</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        FIRE ACTION PLAN \n\n
When fire is discovered:
        •Activate the nearest fire alarm (if installed)\n
        •Notify the local Fire Department by calling.\n
        •If the fire alarm is not available, notify the site personnel about the fire emergency by the following means (check applicable):\n
        Voice \tCommunication  \tPhone Paging \t Radio\n\n

Other (specify)\n
Fight the fire ONLY if:\n\n
•The Fire Department has been notified.\n
•The fire is small and is not spreading to other areas.\n
•Escaping the area is possible by backing up to the nearest exit.\n
•The fire extinguisher is in working condition and personnel are trained touse it.\n
Upon being notified about the fireemergency, occupants must:\n
•Leave the building using the designated escape routes.\n
•Assemble in the designated area (specify location):\n
•Remain outside until the competentbauthority (Designated Official or designee) announces that it is safe to reenter.\n
Designated Official, Emergency Coordinator orsupervisors must (underline one):\n
•Disconnect utilities and equipment unless doing so jeopardizes his/hersafety.\n
•Coordinate an orderly evacuation of personnel.\n
•Perform an accurate head count ofpersonnel reported to the designated area.\n
•Determine a rescue method to locate missing personnel.\n
•Provide the Fire Department personnel with the necessary information about the facility.\n
•Perform assessment and coordinate weather forecast office emergency closing procedures\n\n
Area/Floor Monitors must:\n\n
•Ensure that all employees have evacuated the area/floor.\n\n
•Report any problems to the Emergency Coordinator at the assembly area. Assistants to Physically Challenged should:
•Assist all physically challenged employees in emergency evacuation.\n
    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_earth_quake">ActionsPlans</string>
    <string name="large_text2">
     EARTHQUAKE ACTION PLANS\n\n
        
    Remain Calm. By staying calm yourself, you will be better able to assess damage and assist others.\n
    Take Cover.\n
        If you are inside a building:\n
            \t*stay there;\n
           \t *move under a sturdy table, desk, or bed and stay there;\n
           \t *brace yourself in an inside corner, or doorway;\n
           \t *stay away from windows;\n
           \t *protect your head and face with any available material.\n
        If you are outdoors:\n
           \t *stay there;\n
           \t *move away from tall buildings, structures, and trees;\n
           \t *stay away from fallen power lines, as they may appear to be “dead” but may suddenly re-energize as automatic restoration of power is attempted;\n
           \t *proceed if possible to an open area.\n
           \t *Do not lift or raise any power lines\n
        If you are in a vehicle:\n
           \t *pull over and stop;\n
           \t *remain clear of overpasses, tall buildings, structures, and trees;\n
           \t *make certain your seat belt is fastened;\n
           \t *stay in your vehicle, as it will provide some protection from falling and flying debris.\n

After the Earthquake:\n

    \t*Do not rush outdoors. Many people are injured in this way when struck by falling debris.\n
   \t *Do not use the elevator, and warn others not to use it, because a power outage may occur after the quake has stopped in your immediate area.\n
   \t*Check for injuries or people who are trapped.\n
   \t *Follow emergency medical procedures.\n
   \t *Follow the Emergency Action Procedures for building evacuation.\n
   \t *Assist individuals in leaving the building if it is safe to leave.\n

        </string>
    <string name="title_activity_tsunami">Tsunami</string>


</resources>
